thesportscampus.com 2013-05-01

# Privacy Policy | General

**TheSportsCampus.com Privacy Policy**

TheSportsCampus.com takes your privacy very seriously. Please read this Policy carefully to see how we will treat the personal information that you provide to us either when using our Site or in other circumstances when we collect data from you. We will take reasonable care to keep your information secure and to prevent any unauthorized access or use of it. We process all information in accordance with the applicable India data protection legislation. We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time and the change will take effect once the revised Privacy Policy is available on our website. Please refer to this policy whenever you submit your personal information.

**The information you provide**

We may ask you to provide information to us or collect data from you on different occasions, including at a number of points on the Site, such as when you:

(i) e-mail enquiries, contributions or your views to us;  
(ii) enter competitions;   
(iii) register;  
(iv) purchase goods or services from us; or   
(v) submit articles

The information that you are asked to provide will vary depending on the reason for the collection. In some instances, for example, if you purchase goods or services from us, the provision of certain information will be mandatory.  
Please note that if you choose to participate in any discussion forum on the Site you may disclose personal information about yourself to other participants. If you do so this is at your own risk.

**How TheSportsCampus.com uses the information**

We will use your personal information to:   
(i) respond to your enquiry;  
(ii) acknowledge any contribution that you may make;  
(iii) administer the relevant competition;   
(iv) send information to you;   
(v) fulfill any contract that we may enter into with you; or  
(vi) send marketing information to you in accordance with the provisions set out below.

If you become a customer of ours by purchasing goods or services from us we may send you further information by post or e-mail that is related to your purchase by post or e-mail or contact you by telephone. If you do not wish to receive this information or be contacted please write to the Data Protection Officer at the address below.

We, our subsidiary companies and selected third parties (such as our commercial partners) would like to send you marketing information, by post, e-mail, or SMS. We will only do this if you have indicated that you are happy to receive such information when you submit your details to us.

If you submit your views to us via our contact form, we will circulate them internally for training and management purposes. We may also publish your views on our website TheSportsCampus.com or in other media. If you do not want us to do this, please let us know when you submit your views.

We may aggregate the information you send to us with other data (so that you cannot be identified from that data) and use that aggregated data for administrative purposes and/or share it with other people.

**Sharing information**

We will share your information with our third party service providers only if this is necessary. Such third party service providers are not entitled to use your information for their own purposes. We will also share your information with our commercial partners for marketing purposes (in accordance with the last paragraph) if you have indicated that you are happy to receive such information.

**Links**

Our Site may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of these sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our Site and to read the privacy statements applicable on those sites. This privacy policy does not apply to information collected on third parties' Sites.

**Advertising**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies **,** please see:<http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

**Your right to access the information**

You have the right to access the information that TheSportsCampus.com holds about you. In order to do this please make a written application to the Data Protection Officer, at the address provided below. TheSportsCampus.com may require you to provide verification of your identity and to pay an administrative fee (which is currently $25) to provide a copy of the information that it holds. Please note that in certain circumstances TheSportsCampus.com may withhold access to your information where it has the right to do so under current data protection legislation.

**Updating your information**

In the event that there is a change to your personal information for example your contact details, please let us know of this by writing to the Data Protection Officer and edit your personal details online in the My Profile section, at the address provided below so that we can keep your information up to date and accurate.

**Contact us**

If you have any queries about this Privacy Policy, wish to stop direct marketing by TheSportsCampus.com or its subsidiaries or you wish to access or update your information please write to the Data Protection Officer at administrator@thesportscampus.com.
